myt.mu 2019-08-24

# PRIVACY POLICYWhat you need to know?

                  MAURITIUS TELECOM
                   PRIVACY POLICY
             What you need to know?
https://www.telecom.mu

Contents
■ Our Privacy Commitments
■ Privacy Notice
■ How is Mauritius Telecom committed to protect your personal data?
■ How does MT use the personal data it collects?
■ Does MT share your personal data with any third party?
■ Cookies
■ For how long is your data stored?
■ How can you exercise your privacy rights?
■ Changes to our Privacy Notice

Our Privacy Commitments
Mauritius Telecom (MT) is committed to protect and respect your privacy. We want
to tell you how we use and protect your Personal Data. We want you to feel secure
when you deal with MT that your Personal Data are with a Trusted Operator.
Our commitments to you are:
I. Conﬁdentiality: We ensure that your Personal Data are processed in total
conﬁdentiality.
II. Integrity: We protect your privacy and keep your Personal Data safe. We use
encryption and other security safeguards to protect your Personal Data.
III. Accountability: We view your privacy seriously. We provide support to all our
customers to help them protect their privacy.

Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice sets out how MT may use, process and store your personal
information.
We may get that information from you or with our partners, through contracts or
other legal arrangements you have with us or with our partners to deliver
contractual/legal obligations and for us to better serve you.
In other cases, we will get that information from you with your permission and
consent, or we may receive your personal information from third parties to whom
you have given consent to share your information.

How is Mauritius Telecom committed
to protect your personal data?
MT is committed to ensure a high level of data protection for its customers, pros-
pects, users of its products, services, websites, and mobile apps.
Who are we?
We are part of a larger group of companies and includes:
■ Mauritius Telecom Ltd
■ Cellplus Mobile Communications Ltd
■ Telecom Plus Ltd
■ Call Services Ltd
■ MT Properties Ltd
■ MT Foundation
■ MT Services Ltd
Who does it apply for?
The Privacy Notice applies to all existing and potential MT customers, agents,
suppliers, and partners.
MT and its subsidiaries offer services to customers and deals with suppliers and
partners in Mauritius as well as in European and rest of the World.
The Laws and Regulations
MT is a registered Data Controller with the Data Protection Ofﬁce and is regulated
by the Data Protection Act 2017. MT is also required to comply with the General
Data Protection Regulation (EU 2016/679) (GDPR) in cases where services are
being provided to EU residents, and in the European Community.
MT commits, in particular to the following:
(a) Your Personal Data is processed lawfully, fairly, and in a transparent manner.
(b) Your Personal Data is collected for speciﬁc, explicit and legitimate purposes.
(c) Your Personal Data is accurate, kept up-to-date and every reasonable step is
taken to ensure that personal data that are inaccurate are rectiﬁed without delay.
MT has put in place appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure
a sufﬁciently high level of security in the processing of your data.
Moreover, MT contractually requires that its subcontractors implement the same
level of protection.
MT is also committed to adhere to all other principles related to data protection,
and more speciﬁcally to customers’ rights.

Data Security
We have put in place appropriate technical and organizational measures in order
to ensure a reasonably high level of security in the processing of your personal
data.
How does MT use the personal data it collects?
Information we may collect from you
MT may collect information from you because we have a legitimate reason/
purpose (allowed by law or under contract) to collect the information, or because
you have explicitly consented for us to do so.
Information you give us
You may give us information about you with your consent, for example:
■ by ﬁlling in an application form or sending us an e-mail
■ participating in our member communities
■ participating in promotional campaigns and customer surveys
You may give us information for legal reasons, such as to enter into a contract with
us, when you are purchasing products or subscribing services from us, or when
you are taking a job at MT.
Information we receive from other sources
We may receive information about you if you use any other websites we operate,
any other services we provide, or from our business partners instructed to collect
information on our behalf.
We also work with third parties (including, for example, business partners,
sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks,
analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies,
background checking agencies) and may receive information about you from
them as part of the service we provide, or for legal reasons and to better serve you.
Why does MT collect personal information?
MT collects information for the following reasons:
■ to provide services to you which you have subscribed to;
■ to provide information and recommendations about our existing and new
  products or services that may be of interest to you;

■ to administer and protect our business;
■ for legal reasons;
■ to enable you to participate in lucky draws, competition or complete a survey;
  and to better serve you
Does MT share your personal data with any
third party?
Who might MT share your information with?
MT may share your personal information with third parties, either because you
have consented to same, for better serving you and/or for legal reasons. For
example, we may share your personal information with:
■  MT subsidiaries
■  Subcontractors and third parties for the purpose of the performance of a
  contract that we hold with them or that we hold with you
■  third parties with your consent.
We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to
treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third party service
providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them
to process your personal data for speciﬁed purposes.
Cookies
You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies. However, please
note that when you disable cookies, some parts of the website may become
inaccessible or not function properly.
For how long is your data stored?
MT is committed to store your personal data no longer than necessary for the
purpose for which it is processed.
We will keep your personal information:
■  for as long as required by law
■  until we no longer have a valid reason for keeping it
■  until you request us to stop using it.
We may keep your personal information to ensure that we comply with your
request not use your personal information or comply with your right to erasure.
For example, we must keep your request to be erased even if it includes your
personal data until such time as you are no longer our customer.

How can you exercise your privacy rights?
MT will respect your legal rights to your data. To exercise any of your rights or if you
have any other questions about our use of your personal information, please
contact us.
Changes to our privacy notice
MT may change this notice from time to time and any such changes will be
published here and, where appropriate, notiﬁed to you in writing.
Updated: 19 August 2019
